<Method>
    <Name>check</Name>
    <Category>Resources</Category>
    <HttpMethod>GET</HttpMethod>
    <ShortDescription>Checks whether a user has been banned from any LRG marketplaces.</ShortDescription>
    <Description>
Queries the LRG blacklist to see if a user has been banned from any LRG marketplaces. 
Will return both aggregate blacklistings as well as blacklistings broken down by
marketplace type.

If a blacklisting is found, the reason, date, and severity of the infraction that cause the ban
will listed.

There is no minimum amount of identifying information required, but the more identity parameters provided
the higher the probability of finding a match within the LRG blacklist.
    </Description>
    <Parameters>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>name</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>The user's full name.</Description>
            <ExampleValue>Rob Boyle</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>address</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>User's street address.</Description>
            <ExampleValue>123 1st St. Chicago, IL 60611</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>phone_number</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>User's phone number. Must follow the E.164 format of +[country_code][area_code][phone_number].</Description>
            <ExampleValue>+14157891254</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>email</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>User's email address. </Description>
            <ExampleValue>robboyle@awesomemail.com</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>ssn</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>
User's social security number. Must consist only of numeric digits with out spaces, periods, or dashes.
            </Description>
            <ExampleValue>123121234</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>drivers_license</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>User's drivers license number. Must follow the format of [state abbreviation]:[license number]</Description>
            <ExampleValue>CA:D12312345</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>facebook_id</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>
User's facebook id. Note that this is their facebook user ID, a number, not their facebook username which can be any string.
            </Description>
            <ExampleValue>2031135</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>twitter_id</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>User's twitter id. Note that this is their twitter ID, a number, not their twitter username/handle.</Description>
            <ExampleValue>3456345784567</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>linkedin_id</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>User's linkedin id. Note that this is their linkedin ID, a number, not their linkedin username.</Description>
            <ExampleValue>12498235</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
    </Parameters>
    <ExplanatorySection>
        <Name>Severity</Name>
        <Content>
Each blacklisting is accompanied by a severity. This is a number between 1 and 5 
indicating the severity of the infraction that lead to the user being blacklisted.
Severity codes are set by the organization reporting the blacklisting, and as such are
not strictly standardized. 
        </Content>
    </ExplanatorySection>
    <ExplanatorySection>
        <Name>Reason Codes</Name>
        <Content>
Each blacklisting carries a standardized reason code indicating the reason the user
was banned from the marketplace. The table below gives the full list of reason codes
that can be specified.
        </Content>
        <TabularContent>
            <Entry>
                <Key>THEFT</Key>
                <Value>
A user stole property from another person. 
Example: A user rented a car on a peer-to-peer car sharing network, borrowed the car, and stole the car 
owner’s personal property during the rental.
                </Value>
            </Entry>
            <Entry>
                <Key>MISUSE</Key>
                <Value>
A user abused the primary use case of a particular marketplace.
Example:  A user rented a house on a peer-to-peer house sharing network to sell illegal substances.
                </Value>
            </Entry>
            <Entry>
                <Key>OFFENSIVE</Key>
                <Value>
A user was rude, obnoxious or unpleasant to another user.
Example: A passenger in a ridesharing community verbally assaulted the driver during the journey when the 
driver was not able to drop the passenger off at their desired destination.
                </Value>
            </Entry>
            <Entry>
                <Key>UNRELIABLE</Key>
                <Value>
A user did not fulfill obligations to the community.
Example: A user of a short-term labor community no-shows to an appointment three instances in a row.
                </Value>
            </Entry>
            <Entry>
                <Key>FRAUD</Key>
                <Value>
A user attempted to commit identity or payment fraud.
Example: A user registered to a car sharing service under an alias.
                </Value>
            </Entry>
            <Entry>
                <Key>NONPAYMENT</Key>
                <Value>
A user failed to pay for services
Example: A user’s credit card was declined after several transactions were previously processed.
                </Value>
            </Entry>
        </TabularContent>
    </ExplanatorySection>
    <ExampleRequest>
        <RequestData>
            name=Rob+Boyle&amp;address=123+Michigan+Ave%2C+Chicago+IL+60611
            &amp;phone_number=%2B141512312345&amp;email=robboyle%40awesomemail.com
            &amp;ssn=123121234&amp;drivers_license=CA%3A1231234&amp;facebook_id=2031135
            &amp;twitter_id=3456345784567&amp;linkedin_id=12498235
        </RequestData>
        <ResponseContent>
200 OK

{    
    "blacklist": {
        "blacklisting_count": 1,
        "blacklistings": [
            {
                "marketplace_type": "Toaster Sharing",
                "date": "2010-04-15",
                "severity": 5,
                "reason_code": "THEFT",
                "reason": "Repeated theft of goods from other members."
            },
        ],
    }
}            
        </ResponseContent>
    </ExampleRequest>
</Method>