<Method>
    <Name>user</Name>
    <Category>Resources</Category>
    <HttpMethod>POST</HttpMethod>
    <ShortDescription>
        Adds a user and their reputation data to the LRG database. Also used to update the information for 
        previously added users.
    </ShortDescription>
    <Description>
Adds a user and their reputation data to the Legit database. If that user has previously been added, it updates that user's information.
Whether a user is already in the database is determined by the id parameter. This parameter is the id that your organization uses to
uniquely identify users. 

This method takes a large number of personal identifiers. The more identifiers associated with a user, the easier it is to
correlate that user with other users within the Legit database. As such, always submit as many identifiers for a user as you have available.
    </Description>
    <Parameters>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>user_id</Name>
            <Required>True</Required>
            <Description>
Unique ID used by your organization to identity this user. Must be unique in the context of the marketplace.
If no user with this ID is found in the LRG database, a new user is created. If a matching use is found, that
user's information is updated according to the rest of the provided parameters. 
            </Description>
            <ExampleValue>12344553, robboyle</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>name</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>The user's full name.</Description>
            <ExampleValue>Rob Boyle</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>address</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>User's street address.</Description>
            <ExampleValue>123 1st St. Chicago, IL 60611</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>phone_number</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>User's phone number. Must follow the E.164 format of +[country code][area code][phone number].</Description>
            <ExampleValue>+14157891254</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>email</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>User's email address. </Description>
            <ExampleValue>robboyle@awesomemail.com</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>ssn</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>
User's social security number. Must consist only of numeric digits with out spaces, periods, or dashes.
            </Description>
            <ExampleValue>123121234</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>drivers_license</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>User's drivers license number. Must follow the format of [state abbreviation]:[license number]</Description>
            <ExampleValue>CA:D12312345</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>facebook_id</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>
User's facebook id. Note that this is their facebook user ID, a number, not their facebook username which can be any string.
            </Description>
            <ExampleValue>2031135</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>twitter_id</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>User's twitter id. Note that this is their twitter ID, a number, not their twitter username/handle.</Description>
            <ExampleValue>3456345784567</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>linkedin_id</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>User's linkedin id. Note that this is their linkedin ID, a number, not their linkedin username.</Description>
            <ExampleValue>12498235</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <!-- Method specific parameters -->
        <Parameter>
            <Name>date_joined</Name>
            <Required>True</Required>
            <Description>The date the user joined your marketplace. Should be in the format YYYY-MM-DD.</Description>
            <ExampleValue>2010-10-30</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>transaction_count</Name>
            <Required>True</Required>
            <Description>
The number of transactions a user has successfully completed on your marketplace.
            </Description>
            <ExampleValue>37</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>review_count</Name>
            <Required>True</Required>
            <Description>The total number of reviews given for the user on your marketplace.</Description>
            <ExampleValue>13</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>positive_review_percentage</Name>
            <Required>True</Required>
            <Description>
The percentage of the users reviews which are positive. Which of a users reviews are positive or negative
is left up to your marketplace. This must be formatted as a decimal value between 0.0 and 100.0.
            </Description>
            <ExampleValue>93.0</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>date_blacklisted</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>The date the user was blacklisted from your marketplace, if applicable. The date should be formatted as YYYY-MM-DD.</Description>
            <ExampleValue>2010-10-30</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>reason_code_blacklisted</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>
A standardized reason code accompanying the reason the user was blacklisted. See the blacklist/check method for a 
[full list of available reason codes](/docs/apis/blacklist/check#reason_codes).
            </Description>
            <ExampleValue>THEFT</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>reason_blacklisted</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>
The reason the user was blacklisted. This is not standardized standardized and is simply a plain, human readable 
reason you felt it necessary to permanently remove the user from your system. Allows for a more detailed explanation
than the standardized code provided. Keep in mind that this reason will be published to other LRG members. 
            </Description>
            <ExampleValue>Repeated damage to goods belonging to other users with refusal to assume responsibility.</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
        <Parameter>
            <Name>severity</Name>
            <Required>False</Required>
            <Description>
A numeric assessment of the severity of the infraction(s) that lead to the user being blacklisted. Value must be
between 1 and 5. Selecting the severity is left to your discretion, with 1 indicating the least severe infraction that
can still lead to a user being banned, and 5 indicating the most severe infraction possible within the context of your
organization.
            </Description>
            <ExampleValue>4</ExampleValue>
        </Parameter>
    </Parameters>
    <ExampleRequest>
        <RequestData>
            id=12344553&amp;name=Rob+Boyle&amp;address=123+Michigan+Ave%2C+Chicago+IL+60611
            &amp;phone_number=%2B141512312345&amp;email=robboyle%40awesomemail.com
            &amp;ssn=123121234&amp;drivers_license=CA%3A1231234&amp;facebook_id=2031135
            &amp;twitter_id=3456345784567&amp;linkedin_id=12498235
            &amp;date_joined=2010-10-30&amp;num_transactions=37&amp;num_reviews=13
            &amp;positive_review_percentage=93.0&amp;date_blacklisted=2010-10-30
            &amp;reason_blacklisted=Repeated+damage+to+goods+belonging+to+other+users+with+refusal+to+assume+responsibility.
            &amp;severity=4&amp;reason_code_blacklisted=MISUSE
        </RequestData>
        <ResponseContent>
200 OK

{
    "id": 12344553,
    "is_new": true, # This will be false if the user was already in the database.
}
        </ResponseContent>
    </ExampleRequest>
</Method>